If there are such children in your family who
dismantle any toy into its parts within a day or two, then there cannot be
any toy as strong and durable as this for those children.
This is a stunt car which is
controlled by remote.  Personally,
I like it so much that I have
two such cars.  I got this about a
year ago and it's still
working perfectly.  And I'm going to test these two cars
by hitting them.
Before this, let us see some special stunts of both these cars.
And now finally let's crash these two cars
at full speed.   If we
talk about their price, then you can go and
check it yourself.  Seeing the price, the same thing will come out of your mouth.